Well this whole thing started in the back of a cart
一切都在那辆四轮马车上开始
With this dude named Ulfric in chains
身边有个叫做[乌弗瑞克]的被绑老兄
Captain said that she wanted my head
队长说她只想砍掉我的头
And things would never be the same
虽然我什么都不知道
But a fire-breathing dragon swooped on down
但是一条火龙突然猛冲下来
Hellbent on killing us all
迅猛的屠杀着我们
So I followed some guy and he helped me escape
我跟着那个帮我的家伙逃跑
Though he didn't even know me at all
尽管他对我一无所知
Went on down to Whiterun town
一直跑 直到 [雪漫城]
Joined a troop and headed out to a tower
加入一支军队 启程前往废塔
When the dragon flew in roasting me and my friends
那巨龙飞来 火焰烘烤我和我的伙伴
And we fought him for nearly an hour
我们与他搏斗了将近一个小时
As he finally laid dying All my friends frightened
最后他死去了 我的伙伴们却都在燃烧
His soul poured right into my ass
他的灵魂倾泻进我的身体
A soldier ran up amazed and bewildered
一位战士带着惊奇跑了过来
And then he disbelievingly asked
他不敢相信地问
Do you the Dragonborn?
"你是[龙裔]吗"
The Dragonborn?
"龙裔?"
Do you have that fabled power Of the shout?
"你是否有传说中[龙吼]的力量?"
Go ahead and let it all out
"全力发动它!"
“Fus”
F U S
Guess I’m the Dragonborn
也许 我是个龙裔
Do vah kiin!
I heard this great noise up on the throat of the world
我听到[世界之喉]上有个声音召唤我
So I climbed 7.000 steps to the top
于是我爬了七千步到达山顶
There I met these four men called the Greybeards and then
在那碰到四个自称[灰胡子]的老头
They put me to the test and I rocked
他们想对我测试但我不干
They said that they wanted a taste of my voice
他们说他们只想见识下我的声音
I said “fellas better get in line”
我说“排队不如去干”
They taught me some words and they showed me how to breathe
他们教了我个[龙吼] 并告诉我如何发动
And they said you’re gonna do just fine
然后说"你只要去做就好"
Cause you’re the Dragonborn
"因为你是[龙裔]!"
The Dragonborn
"龙裔!"
Yeah you have that fabled power Of the shout
"是的,因为你有传说中[龙吼]的力量"
Go ahead and let it all out
"充分发挥它的力量!"
“Fus Ro Dah”
Fus Ro Dah
Yes I’m the Dragonborn
是的 我是龙裔!
They tried to take my head
这群家伙竟然想要我的头
and they’ll rue the day we ever met
再次见面他们一定会后悔
Soon they’ll realize their big mistake
他们将会意识到他们铸下了大错
Cause when the time comes to make my choice
当我做出选择的时候到来时
To see which side will have my voice
看看我会如何利用我的声音
Rest assured I’ll choose to make them pay
我确信无疑必须让他们付出代价
Cause when the time comes to make my choice
当我做出选择的时候到来时
To see which side will have my voice
看看我的声音为哪方效力
Each and every time I’ll choose to make them pay
无论如何 我要让他们付出代价
Cause I’m the Dragonborn
因为我是龙裔
The Dragonborn
龙裔!!!
I am the Dragonborn
我就是龙裔!